Hi and welcome to Course 4 of the front-end developers program.
欢迎来到前端开发课程第 4 部分
In this course, we're going to be talking about
本课程将深入探讨 Webpack
Webpack and I am your instructor Alyssa Hope.
我是讲师 Alyssa Hope
I've been a web developer for about five years now,
从事 Web 开发有五年了
primarily doing front-end development and then sometimes full-stack development work.
主要做前端开发 有时也做全栈开发
So I've spent a lot of time fiddling, fighting,
所以我花费了大量时间折腾和摸索
and building things with build tools and Webpack is one of the best ones.
使用构建工具进行构建 而 Webpack 是最好用的构建工具之一
So I'm really excited to be giving this course and I hope that you enjoy it as well.
我很高兴能制作这门课程 希望你也能喜欢
For me part of the reason that I was excited to be
我为此感到兴奋的原因是
doing this course is that when I learned build tools,
掌握构建工具的技能
it was a huge step for me in my front-end career.
是我前端职业生涯迈出的一大步
I began to see websites not as
我开始认识到网站不仅仅只是
just some static files like just some CSS and some HTML that I would couple together,
一些由 CSS 和 HTML 等静态文件的简单组合
I really began to see my front-end as a living,
而是一个活生生的、会呼吸的程序 可以与之互动
build rules and I had a whole lot more control over.
可以建立规则 有更多的控制权
I think that learning build tools really
我认为学习构建工具确实可以很好地
well helps you to see your front-end programs differently,
帮助你以不同的方式看待前端程序
so that is my hope for you in this course and I'm really excited.
这是我希望你能在本课程中的收获 我很期待
To get started, as an overview of this course it's constructed of four lessons.
首先概述一下课程内容 其中包括 4 节课
The first lesson will be on build tools generically,
第一课简要介绍构建工具
why do developers use them?
开发者需要构建工具的原因
What problems do they solve?
构建工具能解决什么问题
Just kind of going over the main build tools that exist.
当然 只会介绍现有的主流构建工具
Then in Lesson 2,
接下来的第二节课
we'll have Webpack and talk about Webpack specifically,
开始专门讨论和使用 Webpack
we'll go into all the instructions of how to set it up and what makes it tick.
我们将详细介绍 Webpack 的配置和工作原理
For Lesson 3, we'll talk about Sass and we'll talk about how Webpack works
在第三节课中 我们将讨论 Sass 以及如何在 Webpack 中使用 Sass
with Sass as well as how web pack works with other professional web development tools,
还有在 Webpack 中使用其他的专业 Web 开发工具
including production and development modes.
包括了生产和开发两种模式
That's one of the big things that you get with Webpack is being
使用 Webpack 最大的优势之一就是
able to create different modes for production and development,
能够为生产和开发创建不同的工作模式
so we'll go into the specifics of that as well.
因此 我们也会对此进行详细介绍
Then finally, we'll wrap it all up with Webpack and
最后一部分是结合 Webpack 和 service worker
service workers and talk about what service workers can do for your app.
讨论 service worker 能为你的应用做些什么
Through all of that,
以上课程内容
we'll have a good chance to let Webpack take us on
提供了一个难得的契机
a tour through all of the most important professional front-end development tools.
让 Webpack 带我们一览所有最重要的前端专业开发工具
A little bit about how I teach.
简单介绍一下我的教学方式
I was a lead instructor of a boot camp for a year and a half so I've seen a lot of
我担任编程训练营的首席讲师有一年半时间 亲眼见证很多
students learn code and go from
学员从零开始学习编程
zero code to professional skills in a short amount of time.
只花了很短时间 就掌握了专业的技能
For me the biggest thing that I think you can do for yourself is to do it for yourself.
我能给出最重要的建议是一定要多动手
For me, nothing beats having fingers on keyboards,
对我来说 最好的学习方式就是
following instructions and seeing it happen,
遵循指导、亲自敲代码然后查看运行效果
I really want you to get a firsthand experience with how
我真的希望你能通过亲手实践来掌握
Webpack works and what it does and I think that will make
Webpack 的工作原理及其作用
all of the concepts that we go over stick a lot better.
这将帮助我们巩固对所有概念的理解
Secondly, reading documentation is a coding superpower.
其次 阅读文档对于提高编程能力大有裨益
It sounds a little silly but I promise it's true and it will help you go
尽管听起来有点傻 但我保证这是真的
really far in your career to just go back to the original source,
阅读原始资料能帮助你在事业上走得更加长远
like see what Webpack writes about Webpack and see how Sass talks about Sass.
看看 Webpack 和 Sass 官方文档如何介绍自己
It's a better way to learn those things,
这是学习技术的更好方式
not all documentation is fantastic but a lot of it is.
并非所有文档都很棒 但是大部分都不错
So we're going to go back and
所以我们会回过头来
talk and read the documentation for a lot of the technologies that we go
阅读和讨论本课程涉及的很多技术文档
over in this course and I'm just going to keep sending you back to read it
这一过程会进行很多次
and get used to that language and the way that documentation work,
让你习惯这种阅读和参考文档的学习方式
so hopefully that will be a good experience as well.
希望这会是一次愉快的经历
Finally, I've put in interview questions into this course
最后 我在课程中加入了面试问题
so you get the chance to practice answering interview questions.
这样你就有机会练习回答面试问题了
Either it will be me speaking the interview questions or sometimes I've
有时我会录制视频来问你面试问题 有时候是直接写出来
written them and it sounds silly but practice them,
听起来很傻 但重要的是要练习
practice them out loud,
练习大声讲出来、
practice recording yourself, practice writing down the answers.
录下来、写下来
A lot of times, I've given instructions as the answer to the interview question,
很多时候 我会给出提示
tips about what you should say,
提示你应该如何回答
what opportunities you have in that interview question.
面试解题的突破口
Even if you're not thinking about interviewing anytime soon,
即使你近期还没打算面试
it's still just a great skill to practice.
这仍然是一项需要练习的技巧
So that's the book of the way that I teach.
这就是我的讲课方式
As one caveat or just one thing to be prepared for,
有一点需要你做好准备
Webpack is a configuration tool.
Webpack 是配置工具
It's not a simple tool,
不是一个简单的工具
it's a complex tool for complex tasks and we're going to take it step-by-step,
而是处理复杂任务的复杂工具 我们会逐步介绍
we're going go really slow,
以比较慢的节奏
it's going to be really easy to follow along,
这样会让你很容易跟上课程
but we are going to spend a lot of time in the configurations.
但是会在配置上花费大量时间
So even if it gets a little tedious, stick with me,
因此会有些乏味 但请跟我一起坚持
I promise that the work will be worth the reward and
我保证这是值得的
we'll be able to make some really cool things by the end of the course.
在课程结束时 我们能够完成一些很酷的任务
Just to give you a better picture of why you would want to take this course,
进一步说明一下 为什么要学习本课程
why web pack is important and what you're going to have at the end of this.
为什么 Webpack 很重要 以及课程结束后你的收获
When we finish this course,
完成本课程
the primary goal is that you would be really comfortable with
主要目标是真正熟悉前端构建工具
front-end build tools and we're going to do that by taking Webpack one step at a time.
我们会通过一步一步地学习 Webpack 来做到
My personal goal for you is that you
我个人的期望是
would get a good picture of technologies that are used on professional teams.
你可以很好地了解专业团队使用的技术
The reason I think this course is the most exciting course of
本课程是整个纳米学位最激动人心的部分
the whole program is that we're going to level up your front-end skills.
因为你的前端技能会提升一个等级
We're going to take you from building just HTML and CSS
从构建只有 HTML 和 CSS 的站点
and we're going to just bring that all the way to what you would actually do in a job.
转变为实际工作中用到的开发方式
So I think that's awesome, I hope you do too.
这简直太棒了 希望你也和我一样激动
When you work with build tools you'll
在开始使用构建工具后
get a whole new perspective on your front-end project
你会对正在进行的前端项目有个全新的认知
and you'll begin to see the whole scope that's really possible.
认识到这项技术带来的许多可能性
So hopefully, this will be a new page for you as you get
希望这是你继续前端之旅的全新一页 我也很期待接下来的课程